(541) 373-5945 🤳

Ryan **Harley**

rharley.dev@gmail.com ≥

LinkedIn in

Github 🖸

Website •

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

I am a full-stack developer specializing in JavaScript and Nodejs. My experience has provided me with a variety of web development knowledge and practical skills – primarily HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Nodejs, MongoDB, React, and React Native. I am passionate about coding and the amazing things I can create with code. I would love to join a team where I can not only utilize my existing skills, but also expand on them.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Audio Engineer

Marriage Builders Radio: Apr 2018 - Present

 Responsible for finding new clients and maintaining client relations. Meet with clients to verify healthy relationship, address any concerns, and talk about future projects and developments within both companies.

GENERAL MANAGER

Kirkwood Crates LLC: Aug 2018 – Mar 2020

- Responsible for finding new clients and maintaining client relations. Meet with clients to verify healthy relationship, address any concerns, and talk about future projects and developments within both companies.
- Schedule daily and weekly goals for company employees. Help on the operations floor by cutting lumber, building, and assembling wooden crates for on- time deliveries.
- In charge of finances and financial decisions, including buying lumber and supplies, create financial reports, manage documentation of business transactions, and more.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web and Mobile App Developer | NUCAMP 2020

Bachelors in Business Administration | Metropolitan State University 2014 – 2017

SKILLS

HTML5	CSS3	JavaScript ES6+	React
NodeJS	MongoDB	Express	Bootstrap
RESTful API	NPM	Git	Agile Methods